yeah?
ん?
Ah, here it comes.
あ、来た来た
Ah, Rin-chan here.
あ、りんちゃんこっち
This way, this way.
こっちこっち
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れー
お疲れ
Don't get in the car.
車乗りなよ
Don't ride from here.
こっちから乗るな
good job.
お疲れ様
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れー
Today, as I promised before, I feel like today...
今日は、前約束してた通り、 なんか 今日、
You talked about wanting to move your body and did a line day.
体動かしたいみたいな話、ラインディしてたじゃん
Yeah.
うん
So I thought maybe I should go get some exercise.
だから、体動かしに行こっかなーと思ってたのね
I have an image of someone studying really hard,
勉強すごいしてるイメージあるから、
He had the image of being quite an honor student.
結構優等生なイメージだった
I guess so.
そうかなー
However, I usually get a bad score on the test.
でも、普通にテストで悪い点通るよ
How many points from today?
今日から何点くらい?
what?
何?
Yeah, but it's normal.
え、でも普通、普通
usually?
普通?
usually.
普通
What about exercise?
運動は?
I'm good at sports, like playing basketball.
運動は、バシケとか得意だよ
What I'm thinking of doing now is the batting center.
今からやろうと思ってるところ、バッティングセンターなんだ
But now that I think about it, come to my beauty salon.
けど、 そう いえばさ、うちの美容室に来て、
Her hairstyle hasn't changed much.
その髪型あんま変わってないよね
I thought it would have grown more.
もっと伸びたかなーと思ったんだけど
But Rin-chan is definitely cuter that way.
でもりんちゃん、絶対そっちの方が可愛いよ
TRUE?
本当?
Try Illumina Color.
イルミナカラーやってみて
I think it would be a good idea to dye it during summer vacation and make it darker again.
夏休みとかに染めて、また暗くするならいいと思うけど
Well, I guess I'll try dyeing it once during summer vacation.
じゃあ、夏休み一回染めてみよっか
It's almost summer vacation.
もうちょいで夏休みでしょ
I don't think your child will be angry.
お子さんはたぶん怒らないと思う
Really?
ほんとに?
Maybe.
たぶんね
Won't you tell me to stop doing that kind of beauty salon?
そんな美容室やめなさいって言わない?
You won't be told.
言われないよ
If you don't say that, I'll dye it.
それ言われないんだったら染めるけど
Not told, not told.
言われない、言われない
Seriously?
まじで?
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever been to a batting center?
バッティングセンター、来たことあったかな?
Eh, first time?
え、初めて?
Well, maybe.
え、かもしれない
Seriously?
まじで?
Well, I'll teach you a lot today.
じゃあ今日はいっぱい教えてあげるよ
real?
ほんと?
That's it.
そっちだね
Yeah.
うん
Anyway, let's start.
とりあえず、スタートします
I got it right, wow, wow.
当 た った、すごいすごい
I got it right.
当たった
Oh, it's delicious.
お、うまい
You did your best.
頑張ったね
amazing.
すごい
Did you do it after all?
やっぱりやってた?
I haven't done it.
やってない
I did it in a previous life.
前世でやってたじゃん
There is also a ball launcher, but would you like to try it?
発球もあるんだけど、発球やってみる?
Firing?
発球?
Yeah.
うん
I can't shoot the ball.
発球のほうができない
lie?
うそ?
Look!
ほら!
I can't.
できない
Haven't you improved a bit?
ちょっと上達してない?
Eh, that's difficult.
え、むずかしい
You'll probably get better at it once you get used to it.
ちょっと慣れると多分、上手になる
It was self-destructing.
自爆してたよ
I was wrong.
間違えてた
tired.
疲れた
You're tired, aren't you?
疲れたでしょ
Rin-chan?
リンちゃん?
I have a work call coming in right now, can I call you for a second?
仕事の電話、今来てるんだけど、ちょっと電話してきてていい?
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
thank you.
ありがとう
Hello, thank you for your hard work.
もしもし、お疲れ様です
yes.
はい
Right now, I'm always around there.
今、ちょうどいつもそこらへんいるんですよ
Rin-chan, sorry for keeping you waiting.
リンちゃん、ごめんね、お待たせ
Yeah, was it okay?
うん、大丈夫だった?
I just received a phone call from an acquaintance.
なんか、普通に知り合いから電話来て
Let's take a break.
ちょっと休憩しましょう
Yeah.
うん
Rin-chan is cute.
リンちゃん、かわいい
TRUE?
本当?
I wish I could be with someone like Rin-chan.
リンちゃんみたいな人とさ、一緒にいたらさ、
It makes me want to hang out for a while.
ちょっと付き合いたくなっちゃう
TRUE?
本当?
keep company?
付き合う?
picture?
え?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm so happy.
嬉しいなぁ
Are you serious?
マジで言ってる?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, Mr. Ishikawa, it's been a while.
おい、石川さん、久しぶりっす
Amazing here.
すごいね、ここ
That's amazing.
すごいっすよね
His name is Ishikawa-san, and he is my senior.
石川さんって言って、俺の先輩なんだよ
Mr. Ishikawa, it's been a long time since we last met.
石川さん、マジ久しぶりっすね
Shu-chan, it feels new, right?
シュウちゃん、新しい感でしょ?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Isn't it cute?
かわいくないっすか?
かわいいじゃない?
That's right.
そう なんですよ
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいっすね
Please take a moment to put on your mask.
ちょっとマスクとってみしてよ
Wait a minute.
それはちょっと待って
Isn't it cute?
かわいくないっすか?
Do you want to go?
か わ いく ない っ すか?
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいっすよね
Hey, Rin-chan.
ねえ、リンちゃん
Yeah.
うん
This person is someone I'm very indebted to.
この人ね、俺結構お世話になってる人なんだけど
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
Rin-chan, let me touch you for a moment.
リンちゃんさ、ちょっと体触らせてよ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なん で?
なんで?
why?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Mr. Ishikawa, isn't it dangerous?
石川さん、やばくないっすか?
nice.
いいね
Rin-chan is a pretty good girl.
リンちゃん、結構いい子だし
That's fine.
いいですよ
Sister, isn't it okay?
お姉ちゃん、いいじゃない?
Rin-chan.
リンちゃん
リ ンちゃん
No, her boobs are quite big.
いや、結構おっぱいも大きいんすよ
It's true.
本当だ
Please change your mind.
かわってみえください
Hey, Rin-chan.
ねえ、リンちゃん
Can you do your best?
頑張れる?
You can do your best, right?
頑張れるよね?
Yeah.
うん
I can do my best.
頑張れるね
Rin-chan.
リンちゃん
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
show me.
見せて
It's okay, there's no one here.
大丈夫、誰もいないから
Look.
ほら
Do you know this?
これ知ってる?
Sister, you know this, right?
お姉ちゃん、これ知ってるでしょ?
Sister, have you ever used it?
お姉ちゃん、使ったことあるのかい?
Do you want to know this?
これ知ってみ?
Want to know?
知ってみ?
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
So, why don't you try using it once?
じゃあ、ちょっと一回使ってみる?
Do you know how to use it?
使うことわかる?
Oh yeah, yeah.
そうそう、そうそう
No, no, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
why?
なんで?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Because I'm not really angry.
本当は怒らないから
Yeah.
うん
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
Is it delicious?
おいしく?
Your mood has changed, hasn't it?
気分変わってきたでしょ?
You don't have to hate it like that.
そんな嫌がらなくていいんだよ
Big sister.
お 姉 ちゃん
Sister.
お姉さん
Hey.
ねえ
It's not great.
すごくないっすね
My current child had something like this.
今の子、こんなのあったやつ
That's terrible.
やばいね
Rin-chan, you're so honest.
リンちゃん、素直だね
Your body is honest.
体素直だね
You said you love me, right?
俺のこと好きって言ったでしょ?
I told you that if you love me, you'll listen to what I have to say.
俺のこと好きならさ、俺の言うこと聞くって言ったよね
Today, with my senior Mr. Ishikawa,
今日 さ、俺の先輩の石川さんとさ、
Do something a little naughty.
ちょっとエッチなことする
good?
いい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
can?
できる?
Then we'll put it on.
そしたら俺ら付けよう
good?
いい?
It's a promise.
約束だよ
You can do it.
できるね
So, will one of your seniors go?
じゃあ、先輩1人行くっすか?
I'll go.
行くよ
Well then, let's go alone.
じゃあ、1人行こう
I'll send it to you.
送ってくから
You can't stand it like this, can you?
このまま我慢できないでしょ?
There isn't.
ないんです
Wow, this is gorgeous.
すごい、これがゴージャスだよね
I agree.
そうですね
difference
さ
Did you want to be your boyfriend?
っ きの彼としたかった?
Well, yeah.
まあ、うん
Will it pop?
ポキッといっちゃう?
Don't you have a boyfriend at school?
学校に彼氏とかいないの?
Yeah, I don't have a boyfriend.
うん、彼氏はいない
What is a boyfriend?
彼氏はって何?
What's missing?
何がないの?
Friends, friends.
友達、友達
You have friends, right?
友達はいるでしょ
Because it smells good.
いい匂いするから
Shall we call it off with my uncle?
おじさんと中止しようか
but ...
でも ...
It's medium to hedging.
ヘッジするのが中ぐらいだね
Yeah.
うん
hey,
ね、
It's been 1 day.
1日 に経っちゃった
Are you painting everything?
全部塗ってるの?
Yes, in a skirt.
うん、スカートに
That's a difficult pose.
難しいポーズだね
難
Yes.
しい
You felt amazing just now.
さ っきすごい感じてたね
Is there a proper tingling?
ちゃんとチクビあるの?
Does it have an adult body?
大人の体あるのかな?
With Chikubi-chan, who has two.
2つあるチクビちゃんと
Yeah.
うん
Uncle, do you like healthy skin?
おじさん、そう健康的な肌好き?
wheat-colored skin.
小麦色の肌
Because it's burnt.
焼けてるから
Look, there's a lot.
ほらほら、いっぱい
It's a lot of chikubi.
いっぱいのチクビやな
Big boobs.
おっきいね、おっぱい
Try holding it down?
押さえつけてみる?
Yeah?
うん?
Would you like to try it on?
つけてみる?
Can I put it on?
つけれる?
I might be able to put it on.
つけれるかも
I might try putting it on again.
またつけてみるかも
difficult?
難しい?
Properly.
ちゃんと
It hurts a lot.
大きく痛いっすね
gold...
金...
Isn't it a golden ball?
金玉じゃない?
different?
違う?
fun?
楽 しみ?
Take this here.
こっちもって
Together.
一緒にね
This one too?
こっちも?
Oh, I'm being washed a bit.
あ、ちょっとおしゆかされてる
Okay, hold your legs.
いいよ、足持って
Hold your feet.
足持って
Take that then.
じゃあの持ってて
Isn't it a gold ball after all?
やっぱり金玉じゃないの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is a golden ball, right?
金玉でしょ、これ
The only person to blame is the one who is hot.
あついてる人しかおせいじゃない、
this.
これ
Look.
ほ ら
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'm with my uncle.
おじさんと一緒だね
See, as soon as it starts to close.
ほら、どんどん閉じてきたらすぐ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
I'll open this up myself and show you.
自分でさ、これ開いて見せていくんだ
successfully.
うまく
It's nice and clean.
うまくきれいだね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do it again.
もう一回して
I'm embarrassed so many times.
何回も恥ずかしい
One more time.
もう一回
Sit down in the asami.
あさみに座って
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
Roll your legs open.
足を巻き開いて
It's from here.
こっちからさ
From here?
こ っちから?
Don't do it.
しないで
I'm just looking at it.
ちょっと見てるんだから
Open it up a little more.
もうちょっと開いてよ
Do you take pictures yourself?
自分で撮ったりするの?
I guess not.
しないかな
Liar.
嘘つき
TRUE.
本当
Liar.
嘘つき
If you want it, it's pretty.
欲しいなら、きれいだね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Can I lick your pussy?
まんぽ舐めていい?
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Can I lick your pussy?
まんぽ舐めていい?
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
Look.
見て
Look, look.
見て、ほら
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
What kind of face do you have?
どんな顔して
Take it like this, this time.
こうやって持っていって、今度は
Take it with you.
持 っていってよ
Please watch it.
見ててね
This is terrible.
やばいよ、これは
これやばいよ
Min-chan's kinta is also shaking.
みんちゃんのキンタも震えてる
Look.
ほ ら
what happened?
どうしたの?
That's what it felt like.
そんな感じだったよ
How did you feel now?
今、どんな感じだったの?
It felt weird.
変な感じだった
I opened it now.
今、開けたんだよ
Does it still feel good?
まだ気持ちいい?
Are you feeling well?
気持ちのついてるの?
Min-chan, how was it?
みんちゃん、どうだった?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
how was it?
どうだった?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Min-chan, over there.
みんちゃん、あそこは
Can you lick me?
舐められるの?
Yeah.
うん
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Do it while sitting.
おちんち、座りながらして
Have you ever licked your dick?
おちんち、舐めたことあるの?
Yes, there is.
あるよね
There is.
あるよ
Would you like me to lick it?
舐めてもらおうかな
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Will you pinch me and lick me?
つまになって舐めてくれる?
With butt.
おしりつき
Do I feel good?
僕、気持ちいいの?
With butt.
おしりつき
Can I sleep?
寝ていいの?
It's okay to sleep.
寝ていいでしょ
I don't wear rubber.
ゴムつけないよ
If you give me a proper butt, I'm sorry.
ちゃんとおしりつけたら、ごめんね
A great burden.
すごい背負い
I went in.
入っちゃった
It's lukewarm, right now.
ぬるって入っちゃったね、今ね
Can you put this in yourself?
自分でお前、これ入れる?
Hold your dick.
おちんち持って
Try moving your hips to hit it.
当てるようにさ、自分で腰を動かしてみて
Does it feel good here?
こっち気持ちいい?
This is working well.
これ上手に動いてるじゃん
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
It feels good, so I pity it.
気持ちいいから、かわいちゃう
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
The bedroom floor is more beautiful, isn't it?
寝間階の方が綺麗でしょ
Where did you say it felt good earlier?
さっきどこが気持ちいいって言ったっけ?
It feels good inside.
奥が気持ちいい
Back?
奥?
Where in the back?
どこの奥?
This back feels good.
この奥が気持ちいい
What?
なんだって?
The inside of my pussy feels good.
まんこの奥が気持ちいい
This feels good.
こっちが気持ちいい
The inside of my pussy feels good.
まんこの奥が気持ちいい
river
かわ
nice.
いい ね
Water got in there.
お水が入っちゃって
Ah, it's freezing cold.
あ 〜、ギンギンに冷えてる
It's true.
ほんとだ
Beer?
ビール?
It's beer.
ビールだよ
Is beer delicious?
ビールおいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
It's better not to remember.
覚えない方がいいよ
But I'd like to have a drink.
でもお酒飲んでみたいな
He was 20 years old.
20歳だったね
Did you like Uncle?
おじさんのこと、気に入ってくれた?
Did you like your uncle?
お じさんのこと、気に入ってくれた?
what?
何?
It's gotten worse since the beginning.
最初の頃よりか落ちとけてるよね
Is it better than the beginning?
最初よりかは?
It's marriage.
結婚だぞ
It's a beer wedding.
ビールの結婚だよ
So let's get ready here.
じゃあ構えよう、ここ
I wonder what it will be like.
どうなんだろうね
Can you hear me?
聞こえちゃうのかな?
It sounds mushy.
どろどろと聞こえちゃうよ
You will be asked about such official recognition.
そういう公認に聞かれちゃうよ
It's okay to say it out loud, that's why.
大きい声出していいよ、だから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Do you like it?
好きなの?
here.
ここ
Have you ever touched it in the bath?
お風呂の中で触れたことある?
Like this.
こうやって
Yeah, no.
うん、ない
cute
かわいい
hey.
ね
earlier?
さ っきの?
cute.
かわいい
Hold this, hold on.
これ持ってて、ちょっと待って
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
This is cute.
これかわいい
Rin-chan, you're an uncle killer, aren't you?
りんちゃん、おじさんキラーでしょ
That's not true.
そんなことない
Looks like he'll be an uncle killer in the future.
将来おじさんキラーになりそうだね
That's not true.
そんなことない
Do you like uncle?
おじさん好きですか?
Uncle...
おじさんは...
You hated it until now.
今まで嫌いだったでしょ
I fell in love with you today.
今日好きになったよね
hey.
ね
Because of me.
私のかげで
what?
何?
This also feels good.
これも気持ちいいんだね
When it's clean.
きれいになったらね
How would you feel if you got it right?
当てられたらどんな感じ?
Is the bed different?
ベッドは違う?
Something.
なんか
Yeah, it's a little different.
うん、ちょっと違う
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
My heart feels stronger than before.
なんかさっきより心臓強く感じる
yes?
そう?
This is the weakest.
これ一番弱いよ
Really?
本当に?
This is the strongest.
これ一番強い
Let's do it like this
こうやってしちゃお
cormorant.
う
Wow, your pussy is so narrow.
すごい、 おまんこ狭いんだよね
It's really narrow.
すっごい狭いよね
My finger got stuck in it.
指が入っちゃった
指が入っちゃったよ
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
good?
いい?
Mitsuto is amazing.
みつとすごい
There is no waste.
無駄がない
Be in a place that feels good.
気持ちいいところにあって
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I was able to leave a tinge behind.
チンチン残せちゃったよ
Maybe I should make myself feel better and laugh.
気持ちよくして笑おうかな
good?
いい?
I feel so happy.
なんか幸せ
Will you lick my dick?
チンチン舐めてくれる?
He even licked both of my scalps.
両頭皮まで舐めてくれて
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
painful?
苦 しい?
Yeah.
うん
It's not even worth it.
きったもないって
Can I fart?
おならしていい?
I don't like that.
それは嫌だ
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Shall I sleep here?
ここ で寝ようか
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Let's go with that mat.
そっちのマットで行こう
I'll give you a massage.
マッサージしてあげるね
massage.
マッサージ
Reach out your hand.
手を伸ばして
amazing.
すごい
Fully visible.
丸見え
It's like traveling again.
また旅が開いたみたいな感じでしょ
Look here.
こっち見て
It's gone.
きったもん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Is the hospital room from earlier available?
さっきの病室あるの?
Yeah.
うん
What?
あ んの?
It's fine without it.
あなくていいじゃん
Won't you come here?
こっち来ない?
I'll go.
行くよ